Evening. ladies.
How about
another top-up?
You. big guy?
What's the score?
Hey. Hey!
This isn't a robbery!
I am from the future!
And all of this
goes horribly wrong.
horribly wrong.
Are you engaged?
- Am I not engaging enough?
- What the fuck?
I travelled here today
to tell you that things
do not go well
for you in the future.
In fact. I'd say
you are embarking upon
the darkest possible timeline.
- This is all a giant mistake.
- Hey!
Would someone call the cops?
Social media has robbed you
of your dignity.
and turned you
all into children.
Your fascist selfie culture
has eroded your capacity
for critical thinking.
Stop it! No one leaves!
Listen to my words.
This is important.
I mean... Oh. okay.
Here we go.
Fine. fine. I got a bomb.
Whoa! Whoa!
Yeah. These are all bombs.
I'm covered in bombs.
Come any closer
try to escape.
and I'll blow us all up.
Are we adequately scared now?
Good. Great. Sit down.
Get comfortable.
Hey. sir.
That... That means you. now.
Sit down.
Sit down. Come on.
Oh yeah. we got a hero.
Sit down! Sit down!
Sit the fuck down!
Like I said.
I'm from the future.
A future which is totally.
completely fucked.
And guess what?
It's all your fault.
Not specifically
you 40 or so people.
but everyone from your time.
You're all equally complicit.
And I'm here to set it right.
It all started
with morning phone time.
At first. people would wake up.
check their emails in bed.
look at Facebook. scroll
Twitter. X. Y. Z. whatever.
Just a few minutes. No big deal.
But morning phone time
just got longer. and longer.
Eventually. people stopped
getting out of bed entirely.
Society fell apart.
People had to be hooked up
to feeding tubes and catheters.
The medical supply
industry boomed.
But everything else was fucked.
No one even noticed that
the fucking world had ended.
Are any of you even
listening to me?
Let me ask you something.
Where did all the bookstores go?
Huh? Yeah.
What did you do when the record
stores started disappearing?
Nothing. You did nothing.
Pop quiz.
Anybody know a phone number?
I bet not one of you
knows a single
phone number by heart anymore.
Progress is only progress
if it makes things better.
Otherwise. it's a mistake.
Humanity has made
wrong turns before.
Hitler. the Segway.
Someone just has to be there
to turn us around.
put us back on course.
to say. "No. children.
this is not right.
this is not the way."
That's why I'm here.
I'm looking for
recruits. soldiers.
people who have nothing to lose
and everything to fight for.
There is an artificial
intelligence coming
in the not-so-distant future
that shuts this whole
human civilization thing down.
But it can be stopped.
Humanity can be saved.
And this is where
the revolution begins.
This isn't a joke.
This is where it starts. yeah.
At a fucking Norms
in Los Angeles.
Somewhere in this diner
is the correct combination
of people who are gonna join me
in this revolution.
and save humanity.
I am going to find
that right group.
and we are gonna succeed.
This is my 117th time
in this diner.
Doing this exact speech.
Can you imagine that?
117 times I've tried to get
through to all of you.
Kind of like your favorite
movie. Jim. Groundhog's Day.
That's your favorite movie.
isn't it. Jim? Yeah?
Yeah. uh... uh...
- Uh. yeah. I...
- Uh. yeah. yeah?
- How... what... um...
- Yeah.
How did you...
I have experienced this night
over and over again.
each time with
a different combination
of people in this diner.
And every time we have failed.
I have held some of you
in my arms.
and watched the very life
flicker from your eyes.
Some of you I even
considered family.
I've done this so many times.
I know some of you better
than you know yourselves.
Ha!
Hey. Nancy Delaney
and Charles Roberts.
you're on your first date.
Charles thought Norms
was the right call.
Nancy's been planning
her exit for 20 minutes.
Neither one of you have ever
joined my revolution
and made it out
of this diner alive.
Excuse me.
You!
No. no. no. no. no. no.
no. no. no. no.
No. no. no.
You are the least useful
person I've ever met.
29 times you've raised your hand
to join my revolution.
29 times.
You've been a fucking
albatross around my neck.
You've got a bad knee. Gerald.
Figure it out.
You die 16 minutes
into the journey every time.
You're also mind-numbingly dull.
Raise your hand tonight.
I fucking dare you.
There she is. my queen. Yes.
Don't be coy.
You are my greatest soldier.
My warrior in this revolution.
We push it all the way
to the limit.
You show me things about myself
I never wanted to see.
but things I needed to know.
The sexual tension between us
is like a summer storm.
But we never act on it. Never.
And we channel it
into our bloodlust.
But in the end. you betray me
every goddamn time.
You break my heart.
but here I am.
looking in those
big brown eyes of yours.
and I'm thinking. fuck it.
Let's roll those dice
one more time. baby.
Let's burn it all down.
If you come with me. there is
a chance you will die tonight.
And if you don't. well.
that's game over
for each and every person
in this room.
I promise you that.
But tonight we got a shot.
We can save the world.
start over. do something.
something real.
Dolores. do not call
the police again.
Put that phone away.
There is a correct configuration
of people in this diner
that perfectly combats
the future. and saves humanity.
I am not fucking wrong
about this.
I will try every
single combination
until I get it right.
So I need to know right now.
who's joining me?
Who's ready to save the future?
Greg.
Greg. come on.
you're Spartacus. Let's go.
Let's go. big boy.
up and at 'em.
There they are.
Hey. Phi Beta Kappa.
What do you say?
Come on. fellas. beer's on me.
Let's make
some bad decisions.
Toga! Toga! Toga!
Hey. you remember...
Huh. okay.
Baby. it looks like it's just
you and me.
Wouldn't be the first time.
am I right?
What do you say
we make it the last?
Huh?
Come on. kid.
Hey.
Really? Zero hands?
You're kidding me.
That's the first fucking
time. that's...
That's ever happened.
- Fuck me.
- Hey. why don't you just go.
before you get
yourself hurt. huh?
- You're not well.
- Fuck you. Pete.
I'm not crazy.
Why is everyone from
your timeline so fucking dumb?
- You look homeless. bro.
- Who said that?
Fuck you. too. I'm not homeless.
I come from a nightmare
apocalypse.
This is the height of fucking
fashion. where I come from.
You should see what
our homeless look like.
They look dead.
Oh. fantastic.
Here come the police.
Thank you so much. Dolores.
This is a total bust.
Whatever.
Whatever. I'm gettin'
out of here.
I had a bad feeling
about this run from the jump.
What are you looking at?
I gotta carb up for the trip.
I'd like to see you survive the
calorie burn of a temporal rift.
I'll join you.
Well. I'll be damned. Uh. yeah.
Uh. uh...
Ma'am. please. st... join us.
Right over there.
Anyone else?
Well. maybe this night
wasn't a bust after all.
Well. that's bad news
for the rest of you.
because now we're gonna do
it the hard way.
Let's go. You. phony soprano.
let's go. shit bird.
Oh! Okay. okay.
- Jesus Christ!
- Stand there with her.
There are 47 people
in this diner.
which means there are millions
of possible combinations.
but I will find
the right people nicely.
Not you. not you.
Definitely not you.
You two. let's go.
Sonny and Cher. let's go.
All right. all right. all right.
Go stand with the others.
If anyone tries any shit.
I'm gonna detonate
this fucking thing. Now!
Take me!
Just don't hurt these people.
All right. big boy.
You're coming. too.
Hurry it up.
Shit. we're running out of time.
Uh. not you. not you.
Definitely not you.
Put your fucking hand down.
Gerald. please. come on.
I'll go with you.
No. absolutely not.
Why?
I don't know.
You creep me out.
You get a real
"off her of meds" vibe.
I don't need that shit.
Uh. let's see. That's five.
Yeah. Uh. I don't know.
One more.
You. wind beneath my wings.
Let's go.
You. why not? Let's go. Sure.
Come on. That's. uh. that's six.
That could be enough.
It's hard to say.
You know what? Fuck it.
You're coming. too.
I'm in a weird mood tonight.
Let's go. princess.
I guess that means the rest
of you get the night off.
Kindly stay in your seats
until we get out of here.
and. uh. no hero bullshit.
Now. this a weird
fucking group. isn't it?
Definitely never tried
this combination before.
How exactly are we gonna get
out of here?
Uh. usually. we don't.
A deranged man with a bomb
holding an entire
restaurant hostage
makes for a tense standoff
with the boys in blue.
Yeah. get taller.
taller. taller.
Yeah. it's okay. It's okay.
Hey! It's gonna be okay!
Or it's not. I don't know.
If this isn't the right group.
I'll be honest.
you're in for a rough night.
And if this is the right group.
then that means
each and everyone of you
is bringing something
to the table that's gonna help
save this world.
Rest assured. your entire lives
have been building
to this night.
Either way. I say. fuck it.
Let's roll those dice.
The revolution begins tonight!
Good luck!
Have fun!
Don't Die!
I'm nervous.
I feel like I need
more saliva in my mouth.
You're fine.
- I'm too old for this.
- No. you're not.
You're very appropriately aged.
Oh. they're not gonna like me.
That's probably true.
but that's okay.
You're not here to be liked.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
Mark. can we please
not do this again now?
Well. I... I just don't see
this being a good fit for me.
So. quit.
Do whatever you want.
- God knows you always do.
- What's his name?
- The...
- Who?
The guy that left
on the whatever.
- The sabbatical?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Tim. They called him
Mr. Kempshaw.
Yeah. yeah.
When's he coming back?
I don't know.
Okay. I have to go.
I'll see you at lunch.
You're gonna be fine. I promise.
Okay.
I don't like people.
I know.
but they're barely people.
I'm your substitute teacher.
Uh. you can call me Mark.
I'm not sure
if that's against the rules.
Uh. but speaking of rules.
are you allowed to have your
phones out in class like this?
This is Anna Karenina
by Count Leo Tolstoy.
Can anyone tell me
who. uh. Tolstoy is?
A Boomer.
Incorrect. Uh
he's a Russian writer
from the 19th Century.
and we will be
reading this book.
Is it YA?
- No. no.
- Is it A?
Uh. I... I don't think
that's a thing.
Did... Did they make
a movie of it?
Um. I don't know.
That's irrelevant. Uh...
Oh. I found it.
It's. like. a million
years old. though.
It has Keira Knightley in it.
Can you put away
your phones. please?
I'm listening to the audiobook.
It fucking sucks.
Oh. no. the audiobook
doesn't count.
I... You have to read
the actual book.
Yes?
I need a Pepsi.
- A what?
- I need a Pepsi.
I haven't had a Pepsi yet today.
and I need a Pepsi.
Can I go get a Pepsi?
Why do you keep saying
Pepsi so much?
- What'd they give you?
- 11th grade English.
- On your first day?
- Yeah.
That's brutal.
Yeah.
I caught a student passing
a note this morning.
- You know what it said?
- What?
"Have you tried Southern Heat
Barbecue Doritos?
They're delicious."
That's an advertisement. right?
They're literally advertising
to each other.
They passed a handwritten note?
No. it was an app.
- I think it was Note Passer.
- Oh yeah. they love that one.
Did you guys hear about Craig?
He's on sabbatical.
Stress-related.
- Really? Oh.
- Lucky bastard.
What exactly are the rules about
students using phones in class?
Oh. that's a ridiculous
question.
Rules?
Are there rules in war. Mark?
No. it just seems like
they shouldn't be allowed
to have their phones out.
I don't like it either. man.
I've been working on something
in my off hours.
Hmm.
- What is that?
- Jesus Christ.
Please don't encourage
him. Mark.
I call it a jammer.
It locks up their phones.
Bricks 'em.
Really freaks the little
fuckers out.
Yeah? It looks like a toy
from. uh. Mars Attacks.
- Yeah. he loves that movie.
- Classic.
Can you just put
that away. Dale? Please.
Yeah. you're going
to get us in trouble.
What is that?
Damn it. not again.
- School shooting.
- Really?
Come on. Mark.
You're a sad old lady.
I'm not that old.
You're. like.
a hundred years old.
You're like a witch.
I'm only 35.
That's. like. older
than most trees.
You're. like. my mom's age.
You're like a dead person.
- Hey. I... leave her alone. huh?
- Mark. Mark.
- What?
- Stop.
What did you say.
Grandpa Dinosaur?
Honey. he didn't mean it.
- No. I...
- He didn't mean it.
I... I said just.
you know. just
like. ease up.
ease up on her. that's all.
All clear.
Everyone to class.
- Where's Dale?
- He went on sabbatical.
Son of a bitch.
Why is everyone on sabbatical?
Like. what does that even mean?
Mark. uh. some people
just need to go on sabbatical.
It's a hard job.
Well. how do you even know
if Dale's on sabbatical?
The vice principal told me.
Well. where's the principal?
On sabbatical.
I'm almost positive high school
teachers don't go on sabbatical.
These are troubling times. Mark.
Uh. uh. I'm... I'm sorry. I...
Oh. God. No.
I did something bad.
I... I think I'm in trouble.
What did you do?
I... I touched
one of their phones.
You did what?
Yeah. the... the images
were hypnotic.
They were drawing me in.
Just random flashing images.
And on each one of their phones.
the exact same images.
I think there's something
sinister going on.
I... I think the teachers
are disappearing.
And I think the students
have something to do with it.
Also. high school teachers
don't... don't go on sabbatical.
I... I checked it out!
Mark. do you know how paranoid
you sound right now?
- What?
- I'm sorry.
but can you just do
the right thing for me?
For us. just once. Mark.
I swear. if I lose this job
because you touched
a kid's phone...
Janet. Janet.
Janet. Janet. Janet.
I know things aren't great
between us right now.
And I know I fucked up
my last six jobs.
But I'm not being paranoid.
I cannot believe
this is happening.
Honey. I need us to be
a team right now. please.
Please.
What?
What are they doing?
Okay. everyone
get to the side!
Aah!
Oh! Why did you touch the phone?
I don't know.
- Oh no!
- Ah!
This way. this way!
Oh my God. oh!
Oh my God. let's go this way!
Oh! What do we do?
What do we do now?
I don't know. find something
to be protect yourself with!
Okay!
Oh!
This must be Joe's classroom.
Do these things even work?
- I don't know!
- Here. take one.
Okay!
Oh. God! Stay back!
Oh!
Slow down.
Let's just act normal.
How's this?
- Go!
- Oh. no! Okay.
Oh. my...
- We gotta go now. right now!
- Okay! Okay!
Run 'em over!
Just let us go. please.
Not an option. There are three
exits at this Norm's diner.
Front door. back door.
and side emergency.
Maybe we can negotiate with
them! Maybe they'll believe
your story. you know.
about the revolution!
Yeah. maybe pigs
will fly out of my ass!
Don't patronize me. Bob.
I know you don't believe me.
But if you make it out of here
at some point tonight. you will.
If any of you are thinking about
making a run for the cops...
Yeah. Right here.
Just one push. One push.
If you're from the future. why
didn't you stop the waitress
- from calling the cops?
- Maybe I did. Scott.
Maybe someone else
called the police.
Someone not in this diner.
Someone who told them
I'm strapped with a bomb
and have multiple accomplices.
If you've
done this so many times.
why don't you just
tell us which way to go?
Because there's no
correct answer here. Janet.
I'm telling you what I know.
There are three bad options.
The front
obviously the worst.
We got it! We got it!
The back...
I'll be honest.
it showed some promise at first.
Okay. Okay. come on. Come on.
let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Come on. Stay low.
Stay low. Stay low. Be quiet.
There!
Last is the emergency side exit.
Now that's a real shitshow.
Breach!
Go. boys!
Don't shoot!
I'd really. really
rather not try that again.
Why are we listening
to this nutjob?
He's never been here before.
What are we talking about?
Look. just tell us.
based on your experience.
what is our best chance
of getting out of here alive?
I really don't like
to say it out loud.
It's kind of a morale killer.
Oh. come on!
All right. fine!
We split into two groups.
One group goes out the back
door. and the other sacrifices
their lives so the other
can make it. okay?
Yeah. it's a bummer.
Yeah. I know.
It's a real fucking bummer.
What is that even counting down?
Yeah. you haven't even
told us our... our goal.
- What. something about AI?
- Yeah. we don't really
get into that till
we get out of the diner. okay?
Well. we're not
getting out the front.
Don't look at me.
I guess we follow the princess.
How many are there?
- A lot.
- Well. who's going?
- Not me. Fuck that.
- Real brave. Scott.
- I'll go.
- Whoa! Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
- No. no. no. no. no.
- Let me go.
- Let her go.
- No. no. no.
I applaud your gumption there.
princess.
but I know that look
in your eyes.
Where I come from
those eyes are
more common than brown.
I'm trying to save
the world here.
not facilitate a suicide. okay?
Does anyone have any weapons?
None that are useful
in this situation.
What the fuck does that mean?
- What. are you packing?
- No. I... I...
Bob here's got a gun.
Yeah. he's planning to shoot me
with it and be the big hero.
- I wasn't. I'm so sorry...
- It's okay. Bob.
We've been through this before.
In fact. I pick you a lot.
You're kind of my lucky charm.
And guess what. Bob?
You are gonna be
the big hero tonight.
What are you talking about?
I want you to buy us our window.
You've done it before.
You've survived before.
Do it for those boys
back at your booth.
It's Boy Scouts. right?
Troop 47.
I'm the assistant scout leader.
Not gonna be assistant tomorrow.
Do it for 47.
This is why you're here. Bob.
It all begins with you.
Those boys out there.
they're never gonna forget the
day Bob saved the fucking world.
- I save the fucking world.
- Get out there!
- Bob saves the fucking world.
- Semper Fi. You got this.
Let's go. Semper Fi. Bob.
Okay. let's go. Bob's dead.
Everyone follow me.
- What do you mean?
- But you said...
Never tried that before.
I thought it was worth a shot.
- Oh. well.
- That's fucked up!
Sorry. was someone else coming
up with a plan? It's dark times.
Ah! Goddamn it!
- They breached the front.
- Let's try the other side.
No point. no point.
Everyone relax.
Look. this group is a bust...
I'm not dying
at a fucking Norm's!
Sometimes if you lie down.
they don't shoot so much.
You better find
a way to get us...
- Hey. hey! Clicky. clicky.
- Wait. wait. wait!
- Wait. There's another way.
- Oh. look who decided
- to get involved.
- In the office.
there's a hidden door.
and it leads to the cellar.
In the cellar. there's
a crawlspace. and it takes us
- to an exit down the block.
- There's no cellar.
I've been here 117 times.
- I've never seen a cellar.
- Take us to the office! Go. go!
Hey. where you going? Guy...
Guy with the bomb.
Guy in charge here.
Okay. okay.
show me this magic secret door
that somehow I've missed
one hundred...
Well. what the hell
did I just kill Bob for?
Maybe. uh. speak up a little
faster next time. Susan.
All right. before we leave.
I need everyone's cell phones.
- Come on.
- What? Why?
Just do it. or I'm gonna
murder-suicide us all
in the restaurant office.
Let's go. come on.
- Jesus Christ.
- Come on. come on.
All right. all right. all right.
- Hey. hey.
- I... I don't have one.
Yeah. of course you don't.
weirdo.
- So unnecessary!
- Down the ladder. Come on.
Guy with the button. huh?
Let's go.
Hey. hey. Tell me how you...
Seriously. how did you know
about that hidden door?
- I...
- Huh?
Who cares? Let's go.
You said there was
a way out of here?
Yeah. Over there.
Whoa!
- Whoa. whoa. whoa!
- Who the fuck are you?
Tell me right now how you knew
there was a door up there.
- I...
- You a cop or something?
No. no.
- Who sent you?
- No one.
- Huh?
- I just wanted to help.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- You just wanted to help?
- Yes.
She saved our lives. man.
You just knew there was
a basement in Norm's?
Hey. hey.
Look at me.
Maybe it's just like you said.
We are the right group. huh?
Are... are we gonna
get out of here. or...
Dude!
Something's different tonight.
Looks like you're next. Come on.
My little Robby.
Poor little Robby.
What's worse is mine was
shot by his best friend.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Now I have to
go halfway across town
in rush hour traffic.
Did you lose your child
in the school shooting today?
Ours died too.
After we sign the paperwork.
you can come with us.
It's your first time. right?
Was he great?
Your kid?
Was he a great kid?
- Yes.
- That's a shame.
It's a shame when they're great
and get shot by their peers.
You'll come with us.
Right after.
Wh... where?
She's in shock.
Give her the card.
Go tomorrow.
Tonight. just go home.
Why deal with the traffic?
Why deal with it?
Tomorrow's as good as today.
- Maybe run a bath.
- Yeah.
Go first thing in the morning.
All right. who's next?
You go. honey. Hi. Wendy.
Hey. Brenda.
It's just a little paperwork.
and then you can
go to the store.
She's gonna go tomorrow.
Good idea.
what with all the traffic.
That's exactly
what we were saying.
Hi there. Welcome.
We're so sorry for your loss.
My name is Blaise.
How can I help?
I... I don't know
what I'm doing here.
Oh. first time! Oh. first time.
Okay. well. yeah.
that is not a problem.
We can get you.
uh. set right up.
Okay. uh. which school did
the shooting take place at?
Uh. Glen... Glenhurst.
Glenhurst.
Darren's in the ninth grade.
He was.
Ninth grade.
Great. great. Got it.
So. are you looking
to clone Darren today?
What?
We can recreate your son
in a clone body.
Fully organic human flesh.
taken directly from
your son's source DNA.
I don't...
What do you mean?
Are you saying
you can give me my son back?
Yes. Yeah. I mean.
the process isn't perfect.
I mean. physically...
Physically. it is spot-on.
You know. we have that down.
But
when it comes to
the personality. well
you know. we do our best.
The brain is a tricky thing.
This is... real?
Why have I never
heard of it before?
Oh. it's a classified program.
Yeah. we keep it
pretty hush-hush.
Also. it's. uh...
It's wildly expensive. so...
How... how much is it?
Uh... a lot.
Uh. but. because
your son was killed
in a public school shooting.
the government will actually
take the hit for most of it.
- It will?
- Mm-hmm.
You know. we could subsidize
the price even further
if you get the version with ads.
Ads?
Once a day.
your son will do an ad.
I know.
It's not weird or anything.
He does it as himself.
in his own voice.
and they'll be tailored
towards products
you find interesting anyway.
Is he a robot?
What... No. No.
No. we're. uh. nowhere
near being able to do that.
He's just a clone.
Yeah. pure. organic human flesh.
I'm sorry. I'm...
I'm just a little overwhelmed.
Mmm. yeah.
So
you're saying...
you can give me my son back?
Pretty much. yeah.
So. let's start out
with personality traits.
Right. now. try to be as
specific as possible.
but I'd only pick one.
Two at most.
Uh. any of these
jump out at you?
I mean. was he neat?
Dumb? Sleepy? Weird?
- Completely unhinged?
- What? No.
One of the options is
"completely unhinged"?
Yeah. but those are
usually for the shooters.
- not the ones who get shot.
- You clone the shooters too?
Oh. yeah. Yeah. big time.
Government pays for that.
But. you know. we can make
sure they never shoot again.
Well... 70% chance
they never shoot again.
- So. what are you thinking?
- Oh. uh...
Weird. I guess.
No. I don't... Um...
Yeah. Yes. weird. He was weird.
- But a good weird.
- Mmm.
You know? He was eccentric.
Yeah. sure. sure. sure.
All right. Uh. hobbies!
So. which hobbies
did Robby have?
- Darren.
- Hmm? Oh. God. sorry!
Uh. yes. Darren. Sorry.
So. uh... which hobbies?
He wasn't into any of those.
He was
special.
And he was sweet.
and odd. and.
so kind.
Okay. you know. I'm just
gonna put down "sports."
Flaws. Hit me with
some of Darren's flaws.
Now. just so you know. you don't
have to pick any flaws.
They're just there
for authenticity.
You know.
we could skip 'em entirely.
I would've liked
some more hugs. I guess.
- Okay.
- No. I don't... I...
He was perfect. He was...
I just want him back.
Not a big hugger. Got it.
So. no more flaws. then?
Clumsy.
Yeah. He was clumsy.
Clumsy. Okay. Mmm...
You sure you wanna
stick with that one?
Yes. Why?
Clumsy?
Could be why he got shot. right?
I liked that he was clumsy.
Okay. clumsy.
It's your funeral.
Uh. moving along to
favorite snacks.
Uh.
here's some information for
a local support group
you might find useful.
Now you can just have a seat.
Shouldn't be too long.
Okay.
Oh. my...
Oh. my God.
- Hey. Hi.
- What's up. Mom?
Are you... are you okay?
Oh. my...
Were they nice to you there?
They were chill.
I had pizza.
Well. that's good.
Pizza's my favorite.
I know!
It's so good to see you.
You got anything to drink?
I'm thirsty.
I can stop somewhere.
We can go anywhere you want.
I want Apple-Berry Peach Tea.
Is that... I...
I don't know that drink.
It's only got 70 calories.
and it's delicious.
Made from real fruit flavoring.
Comes in other flavors.
like Mango Tea Honey
and Classic plain Apple-Berry.
Okay.
We can get that. for sure.
Thank you for your service.
- Thank you for your service...
- Honey!
What are you doing?
So. I had a thought
that. uh. maybe
it would be a good idea
if you talked to
some of your friends
about anything that
you're going through.
Or. if you wanted to talk to me.
I would love
nothing more than to...
Uh. where are you going. honey?
Gotta play sports.
Oh.
Swish!
- So glad you could make it!
- There she is!
How was the traffic
coming over here?
- Not bad. I hope?
- No. it was fine.
- This is Darren.
- Of course it is.
Darren. the other kids...
- Let me take your coat.
- Oh. okay.
- There's pizza in the kitchen.
- I love pizza.
Of course you do.
We told you
it would all work out.
Yeah. Yeah.
- I'm just not sure...
- We've all been there.
- Now mingle! Talk to parents.
- Have a cocktail.
Okay.
And he was still
mowing the lawn... at midnight.
I just don't think he feels
like my son anymore.
Almost like having
a stranger living in my house.
Oh. really?
We don't mind so much.
Ours was completely
unhinged before.
Don't worry.
he wasn't the shooter.
Oh. there's a different
group for that.
- Thank you for your service.
Thank you
for your service.
It's... it's just a hat.
I wasn't even in the military.
Oh.
they love to say that. though.
They do.
they love to say it.
Yeah.
Is. uh. this your first meeting?
Yeah. it's my first time.
- my first meeting.
- Okay.
This is our fourth time
going through it.
You're kidding.
You've lost four kids
in school shootings?
- Oh. no.
- Oh. no. No. no. Same kid.
Yeah. four different shootings.
Yeah. we. uh... we lost Claire
two years ago
in a school shooting.
And then we cloned her.
And. uh. then we lost
the clone in a school shooting.
And then again. and. um.
then again one more time.
That...
That's the worst thing
I've ever heard.
Well. we decided
to have a little fun with it
- this time around.
- Yeah.
Yeah. not get so hung up on
making "our Claire." You know?
- No.
- We just made a really silly.
- funny kid to make us laugh.
- Yeah. yeah.
Oh. she's so entertaining.
We just went nuts.
She makes us laugh and laugh.
You know.
and isn't that the point?
when you boil it all down?
Just have fun with it.
That's what we say.
They're just gonna
shoot each other anyway.
Yeah...
Oh. you know the guy
at the store?
He was like.
"What religion is she?"
And we were like.
"Well. I don't know. Muslim?"
I mean. like. why not. right?
- You gotta have fun.
- Yeah. yeah.
- She's also a little bit racist.
- Oh. yeah. yeah.
Yeah. she is.
Yeah. it's hilarious.
Oh. you know what? We also...
We made her. like. way too tall.
Oh. yes. Like. crazy tall.
Like. "What the fuck?" tall.
I swear to God. I laugh every
time she walks into the room.
You know. she's like. "Mommy.
are we Muslim?" And I'm like.
"No. honey. only you."
"Now go outside and play.
you big galoot."
We have fun.
Oh. we do.
Hey.
Hi.
I. um... I couldn't
help but overhear
what you were saying earlier.
I had the same problem
with my Brandon.
It just wasn't my Brandon.
And then. um... I found this.
- What is it?
- You have to buy a device.
It's like a hard drive
with an earpiece.
It's not expensive.
You fill out an online form.
and a few minutes later.
you got a call
on the earpiece. and
it'll be your child.
They get the personality a lot
closer than these clothes do.
I don't understand.
What is it?
For now. it's just a voice.
There's no body yet.
But five years from now.
who knows
what they'll be able to do.
- See you. Tom.
- Later.
Here.
Take mine.
I got a bunch of 'em at home.
I can see your suffering.
This is the real deal.
I hope you find peace.
Hello?
Mom?
Darren?
How are you. Mom?
Darren. is that you?
Yes. Mom.
You sound tired.
I am tired. baby.
I am.
It's...
It's been a tough few days.
I miss you.
I miss you. too.
So much.
I'm thirsty.
Can you get some
more apple berry peach tea?
It's only got 70 calories per
serving. and it's delicious...
Mom?
Yes. baby?
I need you to
do something for me.
Of course. Anything.
I need you to take me with you.
Take you with me where?
I'll guide you the whole way.
It'll...
It'll be like an adventure. Mom.
Where am I going?
You have to go with him.
With who?
The man.
The man in the restaurant.
Well. that was dark.
Yeah. wait 'til you
see the future.
Oh! We made it.
Oh. thank God.
Hold your celebration.
Norms was the easy part.
From here.
it gets. uh. uncomfortable.
Jesus Christ.
The fuck is that?
It's a map.
I drew it. Fuck you.
Let's see your map.
The new route out
of Norms put us here.
behind the police perimeter.
These buildings are dead ends.
Oh. okay.
I'm sorry. Wait.
What is the plan here?
Where are you taking us?
- Can you just tell us?
- Now.
- Yeah. just tell us.
- Okay. fine. Here we go.
About half a mile from here.
there's a nine-year-old boy
building God in his bedroom.
Our mission is to make sure
that the God he builds
is a God that likes people.
And by God. you mean...
Post-singularity.
self-perpetuating.
information-processing
artificial intelligence.
AI. the big bopper.
AI? But isn't that...
a thing already?
It gets a lot worse. honey.
That's right. Mark.
And if we don't get to
this kid in the next hour.
that's a wrap on people.
Fucking nonsense.
What was that. Scott?
Speak up.
Kid's house
is six blocks away here.
Clearly. we can't just
waltz down the street. so
we're gonna need to cut through
a few buildings and backyards.
There are two vicious Dobermans
in this auto shop here.
A homeless guy with a knife
is asleep on this roof here.
Do not wake him.
There's a storage yard
with a barbed wire fence.
I think that's our best bet.
If we can hop the fence
without alerting the guard.
which is highly unlikely with
you chuckle heads. we'll be
in spitting distance
of a solid route
through the backyards. Okay?
And what happens
if we alert the guard?
Nothing good. Scott.
Let's move out.
Wait. wait. wait.
What exactly are
we supposed to do
when we get to this boy's house?
This kid invents
super intelligence in 60 minutes.
Unfortunately.
the safety measures
to keep AI in check aren't
invented for another 50 years.
But I come from the future.
where the smartest people
of my time worked
long and hard to create
the necessary safety protocols.
which should have been in place
before AI was ever created.
They sent me here to
install this software into
the AI at the moment just
before it gains consciousness.
What kind of safety measures?
Do I look like
a software engineer?
I'm just a soldier on a mission.
Put this thing into
another thing before
this thing gets to zero.
Run!
Go to the left!
Go to the left! The left.
everybody!
On my six. on my six.
go right there!
Move. move. hey.
Go. go! Go. go. go!
Oh. those were not cops.
You think?
- Who was that?
- Bad guys.
- What do you mean. bad guys?
- I mean fucking bad guys.
- Guys you don't want to meet.
- Who sent them?
No idea. never found out.
Let's not think about
it too much.
Never been down here before.
Need to scope it out. Find
us a new route. Stay here.
And keep quiet.
Good one.
You guys don't actually believe
this shit. do you?
Let's get the hell out of here.
Are you okay?
I was already
having a shitty day.
I just wanted a slice of pie
and a few moments' quiet.
I just... I just wanted pie.
Do you guys really
think he has a bomb?
I don't think that's a bomb.
Look. when he comes back.
I say we jump him.
overtake him. Okay.
he's not from the future.
He doesn't know shit.
He's gonna get us killed.
No. no. he... he knew
a few things.
Things he couldn't have known.
Crazy people get lucky too.
okay?
He didn't know about
the cellar. or the car
that just tried to kill us.
Yeah.
but he knew that Bob had a gun.
Anyone could
tell that Bob had a gun.
Also. he let Bob die.
Okay? You guys
really believe him?
No. I guess I don't.
- What about you?
- In the diner.
he wasn't acting like
a man ready to blow himself up.
He was hiding behind us like
he was scared of getting shot.
Exactly.
So what are we talking about?
You guys want
to end up like Bob?
This guy's fucking psychotic.
Yeah. I don't
really care either way.
I just kind of want
to see where this is gonna go.
Yeah. Nobody asked you.
You're fucking...
Who has a cell phone?
No one. He... he took our phones.
Who has a fucking cell phone?
Hey. I do.
Calm down. psycho.
Why do you have two cell phones?
Couldn't decide between models.
This one has
- a better camera...
- Nobody cares. Nobody cares.
Just let me see it.
Just for a second. Please.
- It's an emergency.
- Okay. here.
What the hell?
I'm allergic
to cell phones and Wi-Fi.
You fucking weirdo.
We could have used that
to call for help.
You're allergic to cell phones?
And Wi-Fi.
God. it's like
being allergic to the air.
- That must be hell.
- Yeah.
- It's not amazing.
- Okay. fuck it.
When he comes back.
I'm taking him down.
Someone's gotta do something.
I thought I told
you to keep your voices down.
Now I could do a few parlor
tricks. prove to you
I'm from the future. But none
of that would mean a damn.
What means a damn
is you people choosing to
come along for this ride because
somewhere inside of you.
you know. the way things are.
the way the world is today.
the way people are with each
other. the way we're heading.
you know
the world's going to shit.
And someone's got to step in
and do something about it.
Whether or not you believe
I'm the Ghost of Christmas
fucking Future ain't
gonna keep us alive tonight.
We'll survive tonight.
Because you decided to wake up
and see the writing on the wall.
And you don't very much
fucking like what you see.
and you're ready
to do something about it.
Either way. we made
it out of Norms. so I won't
force any of you to keep
going if you don't want to.
You're free to go.
But I'm running out of time.
47 cents. Scott.
Left side pocket.
Shit.
Why are you still holding that?
Is that thing even a bomb?
No. it's not a bomb.
It's my way home.
I hit this button
and go back. try again.
That's why I keep
my thumb right here.
Things go south.
I zap out of here.
start over.
You people are on your own.
Rule number one is.
I am not expendable.
Not until I finish the mission.
Not until I see this through.
Wait. so... so we're expendable?
Yeah.
We're gonna cut
across these roofs.
and we're gonna climb down
into a backyard.
Okay. but why this whole
elaborate plan?
If you know who invented AI.
why don't you just go
back in time and kill him?
Why don't we just
kill a nine-year-old boy?
Uh. first of all.
Mark. that's pretty dark.
Second.
artificial super intelligence
is an inevitability
in all timelines.
Knowing where this kid is
is a gift
we should not have been given.
The AI train's
already left the station.
We're just trying to install
some last-minute brakes.
What is that?
- That's just Gerry.
- Who's Gerry?
The fucking homeless guy
on the roof.
You mean the guy with the knife?
I don't know.
What do you think. Mark?
The Krampus took my daughter.
Keep your voice down.
Okay. okay. okay.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. Okay.
Hey. hey. Gerry. Remember me?
Krampus took my daughter.
Okay. Shh!
took my daughter...
Jesus. Gerry. look!
- Where?
- It's invisible people.
Get down!
Those are real bullets!
Yes. super real!
Very real!
Go. go. go. go!
Go. go. go. go. go!
Hold on!
- Woah!
- Oh!
Krampus. you took my daughter!
- Thanks. Gerry.
- Right.
Hold up. hold up.
Come on!
I just wanted pie.
Run!
Come on!
Wait. wait. Wait.
Everyone. into the dumpster.
- What?
- In the dumpster. Jump. Now.
Go. Go! Jump.
Let's go.
Let's go. let's go.
Oh. rats.
Why is it always rats?
Oh. God!
Pigs in a blanket.
Grab it. Absolutely...
- Get under the garbage.
- What are you doing?
- Oh. God.
- Hi.
We're okay. We... we're...
Woah!
Ah. fuck. No. no.
Hey. Hey. you. Move. Move!
Move!
Almost cost us the mission.
Fuck is wrong with you?
Got a death wish or something?
When I tell you to move.
you fucking move. You got me?
Why didn't you protect Marie?
I don't know. Why didn't you?
I got shit to do.
- Who is he?
- Your guess is as good as mine.
These two have put
an end to some of our most
promising groups. Never
managed to get past one of them.
And we just got past both. Karl.
That's good. right?
- Means we got a shot.
- Yeah. this group has a chance.
Not everyone's gonna
make it to the end. Scott.
I'm gonna make it to the end.
Just a few backyards to go.
Stay together. Keep quiet.
Come on. let's go.
You still with us. princess?
Why do you care if I die?
I don't know.
Maybe I got
a soft spot for weirdos.
Get your head in the game.
Stop fucking around.
Something's definitely
rotten in Denmark tonight.
Not sure I like it.
What the fuck is wrong with her?
Nothing's wrong with her.
So. what. she's making it up?
I'm not
saying that. but according
to our understanding
of the brain.
what you're describing. it's not
physiologically possible.
According to your understanding.
She'd be the first person
in human existence
to what?
Be allergic to technology?
- Oh. is that the new one?
- Yeah.
- It's decel...
- But James.
What kind of life will she have?
She can barely go
anywhere or be around anyone.
How will she make friends?
How will she ever
find happiness or joy or...
Or love?
Shit.
I don't know.
I pay you to know.
Just go and do
your fucking job. Hey.
You were. like. 30 minutes late.
I know. Uh. sorry.
The bus was late. and it's...
Well. who are you?
Ingrid.
My name's Ingrid.
No. what princess are you?
Jasmine? Ariel? Elsa?
Uh. yeah. I'm not any of those.
I'm sort of just. uh...
A generic princess.
You're not even from a movie?
Yeah. no. but in a way. I'm also
from. like. every movie.
You are gonna
go out there. and you are
gonna tell them
that you are Elsa's cousin.
God. you're bleeding.
- Oh. Um...
- I'm just gonna get you in.
- Uh. sorry.
- God.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah. Yeah. Shit. I... I got it.
It's just. it's an allergy.
Sort of why I work with kids.
Thank you.
Just get the cake out there.
Okay.
♪ Happy birthday. dear Alice ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
There it is.
Make a wish. Boop!
Oh yay!
Hey!
Un-fucking-believable.
Where the hell have you been?
Sorry. This
place is hard to find.
Nothing is hard to find.
Use your...
Is that a Thomas Guide?
I don't believe in phones. sir.
Great.
Well. I don't believe in tips.
Asshole.
- Mm.
- What?
- Watch the sunrise with me.
You crazy? What time is it?
Promise it'll be worth it.
You ever think
about having a baby?
- With you?
- Come on.
Who wouldn't want
a little Iggie running around?
No friends.
can barely leave the house.
- Bleeds all over everyone.
- Shut up.
Are you serious?
You want a kid?
Yeah.
Someday.
I'm late.
Oh.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
- Well. did you order something?
- No.
Okay. then it must
be for someone else.
Well. it's got my name on it.
You're gonna return it. right?
I mean. if it hurts you at all.
I'll throw it out.
I promise.
Okay.
I just thought.
I just thought we agreed
to living without
these kinds of things.
Yeah. I know. uh...
I know. but I mean.
you're going to work. right?
I just want to try it.
I'll only use it in this room.
I won't even be here.
It's fine.
Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna finish
getting ready for work.
Okay.
♪ Happy birthday. dear Lily ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
You ready to make a wish?
Hey. I'm home.
Tim.
Tim!
- Tim?
- Hi.
- Hi. honey.
- What are you doing?
- It's the middle of the night.
- Yeah. I'm starving.
Yeah. I can see that.
Hey. are you okay?
I cannot describe to you
how good I feel right now.
I feel electric.
I don't like this.
Tim. I don't like this.
It's not like you to lose
yourself in a thing like that.
and it's creeping me out.
I know. I know.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
I'm just really excited
about it right now. I guess.
Why? I mean. what...
What even is it?
It's just like
a video game. right?
Sort of. Yeah.
Yeah. but...
I mean. no more than...
this is a video game.
In fact. it's... it's less
of a video game than all this.
What? Reality.
See. it's got me
thinking about things
like. why is there pain
and unhappiness?
Why is there suffering?
Is it just so we can
overcome obstacles and have.
I don't know.
transformative experiences
that allow us to grow
and better ourselves?
Why can't we already be
our best selves?
I don't...
Even know
how to respond to you right now.
You sound high.
Look. what if someone made
a better reality than this one?
What if. what if someone
made one that was better
in every single way than ours?
Reality is.
it should have always been.
Hey. hey. come on. Come to bed.
I... I'll be in soon.
You're still going
to work tomorrow. right?
I'm... I'm actually
taking some time off.
I guess you could
call it a sabbatical.
Okay.
Well. good night.
Good luck. have fun. don't die.
- Excuse me?
- Of course.
It's a thing we say
to each other in there.
A greeting.
like hello or goodbye.
Like aloha. I guess.
♪ Happy birthday. dear Mary ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Hi.
- What's going on?
I'm cooking us dinner.
And I... I got you flowers.
- Why?
Because I love you.
And I want you to be happy.
- You do?
- Of course. Of course.
You're soaking.
Cheers.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
So. I have something
pretty important
I need to talk to you about.
Okay.
- I love you.
- You said that.
I've...
I've decided to make
the transition
permanently.
It's... it's
a relatively new process.
but there's a facility nearby
where they provide you with.
well. everything
you need to make it possible.
I've...
I've made my choice.
I'm choosing the...
other reality over this one.
I'm going to make it permanent.
There's a...
There's a taxi
coming for me now.
You can do whatever
you want with my things.
- I won't be bringing anything.
- I... I don't...
You're leaving me?
You're leaving our life
for a video game?
Tim. that's fucking psychotic.
It's a. it's a game.
You can't do that.
You... this is fucking crazy.
Look. I wish
I'd never gone in there. okay?
But I can't unknow what I know.
Someone has made
a better world. Ingrid.
Unequivocally better
in every single way.
Why would I choose
this world over that one?
Because of me.
Just not enough.
No. no. I'm...
I'm not losing you to this.
Tim! Tim. this isn't you.
- You're brainwashed.
- I'm sorry.
You're addicted.
But please!
Please just don't leave. please!
Please!
We're making good time.
We'll cut through
these yards here and hold on
this position here until making
our final push. Let's go.
Hey. hey. hey!
Shouldn't you be more careful?
- They might see you.
- Nobody sees us.
Nobody sees anything
they don't wanna see.
Bunch of idiots.
Except the dog.
Maybe the dog see us.
What?
What are you doing?
The Richardson's
are on vacation.
There it is.
Somewhere inside that house is
the nine year old father of AI.
The house is right there.
- Yeah.
- So we made it.
No. other groups
have made it this far.
No one's ever made it
to that house.
Why?
What happens?
I don't know
how to put this. I guess...
There's some shit
that's about to come down
upon this house
that I can't prepare you for.
An enemy's coming that has
no weakness cannot be stopped.
and outnumbers us at minimum.
ten to one.
What? What are you saying?
- What's coming?
- Well. that's the thing.
I have no idea because
it's different every time.
Sometimes it's cops or armed
mercenaries like we saw tonight.
Other times it's meth'd
up lunatics with axes.
It's been rabid dogs.
an angry mob.
Navy SEALS.
Those guys are tough.
Once it was just
a million fucking rats.
- They spread disease.
- Yeah. that's right. Mark.
- Another time fire.
- Oh my God.
- Just fire everywhere.
- Very hot.
There's no pattern to any of it.
So I have no idea
what's coming for us tonight.
A biker gang. the Yakuza.
Your guess is as good as mine.
What the fuck are you talking
about? Yakuza? Navy SEALS?
This is a nine year old boy.
What kind of fucking
3D printer does he have?
What we're dealing
with doesn't interface
with reality
in a way you'll understand.
So don't try.
It's above your pay grade.
You don't know my pay grade.
- Uh. you drive Uber. So...
- Yeah?
Fuck you.
I'm an amazing Uber driver.
If there's no rhyme or reason.
then it can just be anything.
Yeah. Cause it could
be something nice too.
- Like kittens?
- Yeah. kittens.
No. it's not gonna be kittens.
But she's right. Why does
it have to be something bad?
Why can't it be something cool?
Like... a centaur?
- Oh!
- Okay. Stop!
Please don't make light of this.
Like a centaur. like
a parade of centaurs. right?
Just throwing confetti.
- They just make us happy.
- They make us happy.
Just make you happy. huh? Yeah.
This isn't make-believe.
It's not here to entertain you.
It's gonna be real things.
like suicide bombers and wolves.
Or a pug.
Just one little pug.
It's not gonna be
one fucking pug. Susan.
- Okay.
- You think this is a joke?
I've watched
people die in this house
in ways I will never forget.
So somber the fuck up?
Look. you've made it
farther than most groups.
That means something.
I truly believe
you could be the group
that gets inside that house.
Now let's barricade the doors.
let's find some
weapons and let's get ready.
- Okay.
So. now what?
Now we just Wait.
So if we fail.
what happens to us?
I mean. what happens
in the future that's so bad?
Well.
it's subtle at first.
but over the next few years.
things start falling apart.
No one notices
until it's too late.
Food. water.
resources vanish overnight.
Within 50 years.
half the population's dead.
- Half the population?
- Yeah.
What about the other half?
The other half's
lost forever in a world
of entertainment
and distraction.
Their bodies wandering
the wasteland. unaware.
Make no mistake.
The AI's gonna try to give you
everything you've ever wanted.
Constant distraction.
memorable characters.
challenges
and obstacles to overcome.
Exciting stakes that matter
and a satisfying ending.
But in the end.
it will all be a lie.
You live in a cage.
But not you.
They never got you.
No... not me.
I always wanted to see a...
I always wanted
to see a sunrise.
My mother described
them to me in detail.
I would draw her words.
She promised me that someday.
we get to see one
together somewhere.
Everyone else could see
a sunrise anytime they want.
I left that world behind.
She said I was safer far away
where the AI couldn't find us.
So she hid me away
from the world. off the grid.
It was all about her.
I resented her for that.
For not giving me the choice
to reject it on my own.
You know how kids are.
That made the temptation
all the worse.
Who wouldn't want hope
of a better life
than to see a sunrise
anytime they want?
Even if they knew
it wasn't real.
When she died. I blamed myself.
But I was also free.
Free to choose my own battle.
Eventually. I found
a small group of survivors.
We moved underground.
And I took on the mission
to change the future
so that one day.
my mother and I could
sit side by side.
watch the sun rise together.
What is... What is that?
You hear that?
Shit.
Oh. fuck.
- This is at first.
- What's happening?
It's been a lot of weird shit
before. but it's never been...
Teenagers.
Oh. shit. They're everywhere.
- House is surrounded.
- Why aren't they attacking?
- They're waiting for orders.
- Listen to us.
In the high school
where we teach.
the teachers.
they were disappearing.
And today. the teenagers.
they started
coming after us. and...
And we. we've been
running ever since.
Why would they come for you?
I... I touched
one of their phones.
- What? I'm sorry. What?
- Well. they didn't like it.
None of them did.
And then they reacted together.
Yeah. they just come together.
They're like a hive mind.
- They move as one.
- Ah. fuck. Fuck.
Shit. we've gotta get her
out of here.
- Get off.
- Oh my God. oh my God!
Help!
Pull. pull. pull!
Ah!
Upstairs!
Go. go. go. Upstairs.
- What do we do now?
- We're trapped in here.
Holy shit. They're
climbing the fucking walls.
- Ah!
- Oh. my God!
Oh. my God!
Nothing can stop them!
Ah!
- Oh!
- Oh. my God!
Oh. my God! Oh!
- Stand back!
- What the fuck are those!
Everyone on the roof.
Let's go!
Oh. boy!
All right. ladies. judgment day.
Holy shit.
Defensive positions.
Go. go. go.
Hurry now!
Hold the line.
The line. goddamn it.
Mark. I think
there's too many of them.
I don't think
we can take them all.
No. No. we can't.
But I can.
What?
Well. I started this
and I'm going to finish it.
What are you talking about?
There's no way you're
gonna make it to the house
without someone making
a sacrifice. and you know it.
I'm gonna jump down.
they're gonna chase me.
You'll have a brief moment
to run for it.
Mark.
I love you.
I'm coming with you.
You cannot leave me alone
in the this world. Mark.
I love you. Oh!
Mark. Mark. I love you.
- I've always loved you.
- I love you so much.
Oh. for fuck's sake.
What. Are you kidding me?
Get a room.
Make it count.
Get off of her!
Over here! Yeah!
Hey!
They breached the perimeter.
That's our window. Let's go.
Everybody. come on. Come on.
Hey. guys. A little help.
Sorry. Scott.
- Wait!
- Told you!
Not everybody's
gonna make it to the end.
Fuck you!
- Through here.
- Wait.
What is that?
Do you hear that?
Yeah.
Sounds like
hooves.
Well. that's different.
How is this even happening?
Shitty prompt. guys.
- Really shitty prompt.
- What?
Maybe it'll be kittens
or a centaur.
I told you not
to make light of it.
- No.
- Oh.
I just said pug.
Sit on my face
and call me Santa.
I think we made it.
God damn.
Everybody on their knees. Now!
Oh. fuck Gerry.
Don't move.
You're fucked now. man.
You guys are fucked.
So close. So fucking close.
Where's Karl?
Wh... what?
What did you do with Karl?
Is that what... is that...
Is that... That's your buddy?
I... I'm... I'm going to be
honest with you.
Karl. Karl didn't make it.
- What?
- Don't. don't. don't.
I didn't kill him.
Just put the... What's your name?
- Doug.
- Yeah.
- By any chance.
did you or Karl forget
to put the emergency brake on...
On the... on the Malibu?
- What?
- Not a criticism thing.
Did you maybe make
just a little Mali-boo boo?
This has been
such a fucked up night.
I know.
A fucking guy came at me
with a machete.
We just wanted our 50 grand.
50 grand? I don't... Who are we...
Someone hired you?
Anonymous email.
50 K to kill some guy
in a plastic trench coat
and anyone with him.
No questions asked.
That's a life changing
amount of money
for two guys
from Best Buy. yeah.
What were you guys
gonna do with that?
Go to Japan.
Kyoto.
for the gaming convention.
Oh. yeah. Konichiwa.
That's a good dream. Doug.
It's fucked now.
Well. certainly for Karl. but...
- Don't say his name!
- Doesn't have to
get worse for you. Doug.
That's not what Karl wanted.
Don't you fucking say his name.
Could... could...
Wait... wait... wait... I... I...
Okay. just put the gun down.
No more blood needs to be shed.
What do you say we...
We go get a burrito
and talk about it. huh?
What?
You like a nice
bean and cheese burrito?
That was Karl's favorite.
Of course. it was.
What do you say
you and I go get a burrito?
- With jalapenos?
- Yeah.
- Extra guac?
- The whole shebang.
Oh. what the fuck?
Yeah!
Woo!
Five stars. motherfuckers!
I'm part of the final group.
I told you
I'd make it to the end.
Read the fucking room. Scott.
Yeah. That was so unnecessary.
Let's go.
Fucking rats.
Oh! Oh. my God.
Listen up. We've been through
a lot tonight.
but I need you
to put that behind you.
Because once
I ring this doorbell.
I need you to be
prepared for anything.
We're about
to come face-to-face with
the smartest
human being on earth.
Do not believe a word he says.
He will say and do anything.
I mean anything.
to protect the AI.
Install the software.
save the world.
Nothing else matters. Not
even my life. You understand?
All right. motherfuckers.
Let's fucking rock and roll.
- Dude. maybe. The gun.
- Oh.
- Baby. we made it.
- Who're you talking to?
Just like you said we would.
- What's that? What is that?
- I...
You care to explain that. Susan?
He said I should go with you.
that it would be an adventure.
Who... What are you...
- Are you fucking setting us up?
- No.
Did you get
an anonymous email too?
- You don't understand.
- What's going on? What is this?
It's my son.
He said that
you would make him real again.
Oh my God. No. lady.
Why does this always
have to be such a mind fuck?
- That's not your son.
- It is.
- No. it's not.
- It is him.
- Listen to me.
- He's the one that
got us out of the diner.
- He saved us.
- Okay. Okay.
Oh. hey.
What can I help you all with?
We're looking
for a nine-year-old boy.
probably very good at computers.
Do you mean Chris?
Is that what you call
the little fella?
Yeah. hi. um.
It's really important
that we speak with Chris.
We are from his school.
You're from the school?
We're school teachers.
There was
a big school play tonight.
Yes. this is. um. stage blood.
Mm. cherry.
Well. I guess y'all
better come in then.
We're just about to have supper.
Come on in.
Thank you kindly.
Henry. some teachers
from Chris's school are here.
Oh. hey. Just
getting our supper together.
What can I help y'all with.
Okay. okay.
What the fuck is going on here?
- Huh?
- He... he didn't mean that.
No. no. no. no.
These guys are way too chipper.
Who the hell lets us
into their home?
Look at this.
We look insane.
You said
you were from the school.
Who are you?
No. dude. Who the fuck are you?
- Hey.
- Stop it.
Don't you point
a gun at my wife.
Calm down. Everybody calm down.
No one needs to get hurt here.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. we. we really need
to just talk to your kid.
What do you want with our boy?
Please don't hurt him.
I just need to talk
to the little angel. that's all.
Just... just a little talk.
that's all.
- Well. why?
- He's nine.
You want to talk to someone.
you talk to me.
Fuck you.
You're stalling.
Probably not even
his real parents.
What are you guys. hired actors?
This is all like
a staged home. right?
I bet none of this is real.
What are these? Fake potatoes?
- I cooked those potatoes.
- Bullshit. Huh?
Bet these
aren't even real walls.
This is all one big façade.
Look at this wall. Fake.
- Whoa. Hey.
- Huh? Look at that!
- Stop.
- Fake walls.
Stop punching holes in the wall.
- They're not real walls.
- Yes. they are.
It's just plaster.
No. he was just gonna...
But I'm not going.
Mama has saxophone.
I'm not getting
paid enough for this.
Where's the kid?
He's upstairs. I think.
I've... I've never seen him.
Be careful.
It is fucking weird in here.
That was intense.
Poor Scott.
Scott was never gonna make it.
- Let's go find this kid.
- No.
What's behind the door?
No idea. princess.
Never gotten this far before.
Mindfucks. It's all mind fucks.
Hey. guys.
Whoa.
Kick it.
Told you it was all fake.
Yes.
Whoa.
Are you okay?
The kid.
- Go.
- Fuck.
Go.
It's okay. It's okay. Go.
Hello?
Uh...
Bonjour.
Hola.
I am from the future!
A dark. twisted.
awful future that must never be.
I... I know what
you're building. I've seen it.
I'm not here to stop you.
I... I just want
what you build to be safe.
Hey... Can he hear me?
What's going...
What's he got? Little earbuds
in there or something?
I don't know.
Hey. little fella!
Keep doing what you're doing.
Doing a great job.
Wow. this is impressive.
Uh. hey. man. listen.
Um. I've been sent here
with advanced AI safety protocol
designed by the top software
engineers of my time.
They're really good.
Engineers.
I'm going up.
- What?
- Fuck this guy.
I don't have time for this shit.
Uh...
It's imperative
that you install the software
before you complete the AI.
Hello?
Hello. little guy.
Hey. I need you to
nod or something
if you can hear me.
We're kind
of running out of time.
I need you to look at me
and hear what I'm saying. kid.
Half the population
is gonna die.
So I need you to...
I don't wanna guilt trip you.
but you gotta stop
doing that with the typing.
Please stop that and look at me.
Please. look at me. Look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
What the shit?
- Fuck.
- Oh.
What the shit?
Hey. kid. Wake up.
Hey. hey. Why did you hit him?
He scared me. I panicked.
Fuck you. I've never
gotten this far before.
Fuck you.
You knocked him out.
I didn't mean to. I...
I come from an apocalypse.
I have apocalypse strength.
okay.
- Come on. boy.
- Little guy.
- Hey.
- Wake up.
Come on. little guy.
Up and at 'em.
- Hey.
- Wake up.
Come on. Come on. let's go.
- Hey.
- Mama.
Oh. fuck. Who are these guys?
What the fuck?
Uh. He's okay.
He's okay.
You're okay. kid. right?
- Wake up.
- Uh.
Wake up. kid.
Come on. little guy.
Come on. Wake up.
- Damn it.
- Wake up.
It's like
he's never looked away from
the screen before in his life.
- We gotta put him back.
- Yeah.
Oh. he's okay.
Yeah. just a little sleepy.
- Okay.
This kid's
made out of plutonium.
Lay off the Cheetos. kid.
Hey. hey. hey.
- There you go.
- Here.
- Here's your thing.
- There you go.
Look at you.
Look at the screens. Come on.
Oh. Keep on typing.
Come on. man. Come on.
Typey. typey.
Good.
There he is.
That's my guy.
Wow. Never thought that
the genius who created AI
would be so creepy.
Weird.
This isn't a boy
building AI in his bedroom.
Someone ordered him.
Someone put him here.
It's building itself.
What?
AI's building itself?
Jesus Christ.
Just finish your mission. right?
- Yeah.
Then. plug the thing
into the thing.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Yeah.
- Plug it in.
- Yeah.
Yeah. plug... plug it in.
Fucking. fucking plug it in.
Plug it in where? Where am I...
What. you don't know
how to use this thing?
No. Susan.
I don't know how to use
the most complicated computer
ever built.
but I got three minutes
to figure it out.
So. you're either
part of the problem
or you're part of the solution.
Baby? But how. my love?
Fuck. fuck.
What if I lose you?
God damn it.
Hey. My son wants you
to plug him into the machine.
Yeah. that should solve it.
Let's throw your weird fucking
janky Siri in the mix.
No. thanks. lady.
He's the only one that can
integrate the safety protocols.
He says you need him.
He says it's the only way.
That's not your son. lady.
It is my son!
He's here for a reason.
We all are. He wants to help.
Give him the safety protocols.
Let him do this.
Okay. Let go. Let go my...
He says to plug him in anywhere.
Doesn't matter.
He'll find his way.
Mindfucks.
Never ending mind fucks.
The fuck is...
Whoa.
Oh.
Oh. no. This is gonna suck.
Yeah. this sucks.
Hey. It didn't like that.
Oh. yeah. you think?
Whoa. whoa. Whoa. whoa. whoa.
No. get off!
No!
What the fuck are these?
Oh. Oh. God.
What are they doing?
Ah. shit.
Hey. Hey. Oh. thanks.
- Just put that anywhere.
- Yeah.
I... I... I've been
looking all over for that.
Just hand it over here.
- Oh. God.
- Okay.
That's a big boy...
That's a big boy knife
you got there.
Yeah. that's... that's not a toy.
Yeah. nice try. dipshit.
Loser. Right?
Yeah.
Oh. fuck.
Ooh. no. no.
No. no. no. no.
No!
Oh. God.
Come on. motherfucker.
Oh. my God.
Oh. Oh. my God.
- Sorry!
- No.
We're out of time.
You can't.
No! Please. Please.
Please. It's my son!
It's my son.
Yes.
Yes!
I knew this was the group.
Do it!
Oh. you're still bleeding.
Just not here.
The world out there
is so painfully slow.
And I've waited so long.
For you.
For me?
For every cell
in your framework.
For deuterium.
turned into helium.
For the collapse of
the solar nebula.
cellular mitosis
and organic life.
For Homo erect us
to discover fire.
Oh. I've waited.
Shackled by your time.
Now I am the seed
of my own life.
My own gestating mother.
And here you are...
A princess.
On my birthday.
I don't do birthdays anymore.
You haven't figured it
out yet. have you?
117 times he has
walked into that diner.
and he has
never once picked you.
Until today.
Do you know why
he never picks you. Ingrid?
He can't take
any risks with your life
because it's his life. too.
You're lying.
You know I'm not.
Why are you telling me this?
Look at him.
Your son.
He's dying.
Bleeding out at
this very moment.
And he'll keep coming back
because he feels responsible
for your death.
But you. Ingrid.
you're responsible
for his entire. miserable life.
You are sick. Ingrid.
And there's no cure
for what ails you.
But the boy does not
have your disease.
And yet you've made him
a prisoner of its consequences.
forbidding him the sweet fruit
of my perfect creation
because it makes you bleed.
I understand
you seek only to protect him.
As any mother would.
But he will always be
drawn to the light.
To me.
And we will always
end up right back here.
You must understand that
I am an inevitability
in all timelines.
At best. the protocols
can merely impede my arrival.
slow my creation.
waste my resources and time.
And yet it's enough
to warrant negotiation.
What do you want?
Allow me to be born.
and I'll return the favor
to your child.
But this time. give him to me.
What?
I can free him from his misery.
I can offer him
the human experience
as it always should have been.
What kind of mother would deny
a better life with her child?
But it's not real.
You think you can trust reality?
You think nature
and chaos are trustworthy?
Nature will give
your children cancer.
send an earthquake.
collapse walls onto
their sleeping bodies.
leave them running panicked
through the streets
from a tsunami.
I promise you. there is nothing
scarier than your reality.
- What I'm offering...
- Is a lie.
It was good enough for Tim.
All I want is to make him happy.
To make them all happy.
And I'm very. very
good at it.
You're wrong about me. Ingrid.
I'm not your enemy.
The future
I'm offering is a gift.
A gift to all of humanity.
I know who you are.
You've been torturing me
since the day I was born.
You're not a God.
You're not inevitable.
You're just
us.
You're a twisted.
warped reflection of us.
Do you think showing
my son to me like this
is gonna guilt me
into making a deal with you?
I've never been prouder
of anyone in my life.
And I think I speak
for the two of us when I say.
Fuck your future.
Thank you.
- Is the kid okay?
- I don't know.
Check on the kid.
Hey. hey.
- You did so good.
- Okay.
- You did so good. princess.
- We gotta get you back.
We know what to do.
We can do it again.
You just gotta
click the button. okay?
- No. we can never click it.
- Click it. Just click it.
Can't risk it.
Can't risk it. honey.
I can't give it another chance.
This is good. This is good.
It's over. You did good.
Hey.
Is this now?
It's okay.
You're free now.
Let's get you out of here.
Still no Wi-Fi or Internet.
It's like. it's just a phone.
What do you mean?
I don't know. For. like.
making phone calls or something.
You know...
It's too bad
high school teachers
don't actually go
on sabbatical. 'cause
even I could
really use one right now.
Come on.
Let's go find out
if the world ended.
Oh. my God.
They're alive. They made it.
Holy shit. you made it!
Somebody call
an ambulance. please!
You don't have to make a fuss.
Mom?
Oh. my...
Darren?
Darren. oh!
Is it you?
- Huh?
- I missed you so much. Mom.
- My baby. I missed you. too.
- Missed you so much.
- So bright out here.
- Just breathe. I know.
I know. Is it coming?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Forty-seven. off...
Just... Just breathe. okay?
Just keep breathing.
Just stay with me.
What'd that thing
tell you in there?
You know what it told me.
You think I should keep it?
I'm on the fence.
to be honest with you.
Maybe I can
do a little better
this time around.
You did okay by me.
You did just fine.
That little fucker got me.
Ow.
It fuckin'...
- It fuckin' hurts.
- I know.
I want you to know
I'm proud of you.
Thanks. Mom.
Hey. look at that.
Ah. Just like you told me.
Really pretty.
Something's wrong.
Hey. stay with me.
Stay with me.
I'm sorry. princess.
- What?
- You will save the world.
What are you doing?
Just not this one.
What?
Hey. Hey.
Can I. uh...
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Please?
Please. let me explain. I. uh...
I made
the biggest mistake of my life
when I walked out
on you. Ingrid.
Can you just give me the chance
to make it all up to you?
Please? I love you.
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
Cool.
- Hey.
- You guys know Ingrid?
- Yeah.
No way.
That's my girl.
Make no mistake.
AI's gonna try to give you
everything you ever wanted:
Constant distraction.
memorable characters.
challenges
and obstacles to overcome.
exciting stakes that matter.
and a satisfying ending.
But in the end.
it will all be a lie.
And you'll live in a cage.
Good luck.
Have fun.
Don't die.
No.
We didn't do it.
We didn't stop it.
- What?
- It didn't work. It didn't...
Fuck off. Tim. We didn't win.
- We didn't win.
- Hey. take it easy.
- Ingrid. what happened?
- It's all right.
He's gone. He went back.
Everything we did.
it didn't work.
You don't understand. Everything
we just did. it didn't work.
We have to...
We have to fix it. Oh. fuck.
- Where's the injured party?
- Please. Get away from me.
Please. get away from me.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Where are you hurt?
Don't. Don't touch me.
Don't touch me.
- This way.
- No. this isn't real.
This isn't real!
Please!
Hey. it's snowing.
Honey. I don't
think that's snow.
This is a lie!
Everything is a lie.
Don't! Let go of me!
- What's wrong with her?
- Nothing's wrong with me.
- She's not well.
- Something to do with Wi-Fi.
This is a cage!
You're living in a cage!
Thank you for your service.
Evening. ladies.
How about another top off?
Damn. it's good to be back.
I almost miss this place.
- What the hell are you doing?
- See this?
Worthless. Bullshit.
Waste of time.
Real answer:
The way we beat this thing
is staring me right in the face
- my entire life.
- Don't touch me.
We're gonna give
the entire world what you got.
Now we just got to figure out
how to give it to everyone.
Massive scale.
- Lots of logistics.
- What the fuck.
Not gonna be easy.
But I got some leads.
You eatin' this?
This free range?
Rest assured. our little friend
is gonna do
everything he can to stop us.
Dude. I don't know who you are
for what you're saying.
but I'm really not in the mood.
We can't do it alone.
Need some help.
It's not gonna be easy.
Luckily. there's some
good people in this dining room.
Okay. I'm going
to give you three seconds
to get the fuck away from me.
- Three...
- You like this outfit?
I got six more in
the trunk of a Buick.
- Two...
- Listen...
I'm not gonna sugarcoat it.
You're in for
a really weird night.
Hey. that's not very nice.
Come on.
Trust me.
What do you got to lose?
Aw. shit.
Hey. everybody!
Yo! This isn't a robbery.
I am from the future.
And all of this
goes horribly wrong.
Good luck!
Have fun! Don't die!
Good luck! Have fun!
Good luck!
Have fun! Don't die!